{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Ken is ___ his older brother.",
      "a": "as tall a fellow as",
      "b": "as a tall fellow as",
      "c": "taller a fellow than",
      "d": "so tall a fellow as",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- As + adj/adv (noun) + as: used when you are comparing two people, things, situations etc ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "18",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tim is ___ to know the fact.",
      "a": "probable",
      "b": "likely",
      "c": "probably",
      "d": "maybe",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Likely to do/be something: something that is likely will probably happen or is probably true",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "18",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you think that the bill will be passed? \"Oh, yes. It's ___ that it will.\"",
      "a": "near possible",
      "b": "almost surely",
      "c": "quite certainly",
      "d": "very likely",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Likely (to do/be something): something that is likely will probably happen or is probably true ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "18",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The soprano is _________ the three.",
      "a": "the wealthier of",
      "b": "wealthiest from",
      "c": "the wealthiest between",
      "d": "the wealthiest of",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Superlative you talk about one thing only and how it is the best, worst, etc. You do not compare two things \n+ The most+ adj/ adj+est (of) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "18",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The opera is ___ watching.",
      "a": "well worthy",
      "b": "very worth",
      "c": "well worth",
      "d": "good worth",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": ".\n- Well worth doing sth:  used to say that something is interesting, useful, or helpful",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "18",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I did what I should do, so I didn't feel ___ the praise.",
      "a": "worth being",
      "b": "worthy",
      "c": "worth of",
      "d": "worthy of",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": ".\n-Feel/ be worthy of something:  to deserve to be thought about or treated in a particular way",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "18",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The firefighters pushed the door ___ they could.",
      "a": "as hardly as",
      "b": "as hard as",
      "c": "so hardly as",
      "d": "so hard as",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Hard (adj) : firm, stiff, and difficult to press down, break, or cut \n- Hardly (adv): almost not",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "18",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The children rolled the wheels ___ they could.",
      "a": "as quickly as",
      "b": "so far as",
      "c": "more faster than",
      "d": "as fast as",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": ".\n- So ...as= as ...as (so....as is used in negative sentences, while as.... as.... is used in affirmative ones)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "18",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The cost of one meal in an average restaurant can run ___ 50~100.",
      "a": "as high as",
      "b": "as far as",
      "c": "so much as",
      "d": "as expensive as",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- We often use \"high\" with \"cost\" \n- As + adj /adv + as: To the degree or extent that",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "18",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "For certain uses there is no metal ___ steel.",
      "a": "as well as",
      "b": "as strong as",
      "c": "as long as",
      "d": "as good as",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": ".\n- Comparison of Equality: as + adj/adv + as",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "18",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}